ezfacility.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy | EZFacility

EZFacility, Inc. ("EZFacility" or the "Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. This Privacy Statement describes EZFacility’s information practices.

EZFacility complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union member countries. EZFacility has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view EZFacility’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

EZFacility has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal.

The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.ezfacility.com and does not cover information that may be collected through our [mobile applications] [social networking applications] [behind the log in on our website].

### Web Sites Covered

This Privacy Statement covers the information practices of Web sites that link to this Privacy Statement: [http://www.ezacility.com](http://www.ezacility.com/).

EZFacility’s Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. EZFacility is not responsible for the information practices or the content of such other Web sites. The Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of other Web sites to understand their information practices.

### Personal Information Collected

EZFacility offers a variety of services that are collectively referred to as the "Service." EZFacility collects information from individuals who visit the Company’s Web sites ("Visitors") and individuals who register to use the Service ("Customers").

When expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Service or registering to use the Service, EZFacility requires you to provide the Company with contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address ("Required Contact Information"). When purchasing the Service, EZFacility requires you to provide the Company with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the Service ("Billing Information"). EZFacility may also ask you to provide additional information, such as company annual revenues, number of employees, or industry ("Optional Information"). Required Contact Information, Billing Information, and Optional Information are referred to collectively as "Data About EZFacility Customers."

As you navigate the Company’s Web sites, EZFacility may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons ("Web Site Navigational Information"). Web Site Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and the actions you take on the Company’s Web sites (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked).

### Use of Information Collected

The Company uses Data about EZFacility Customers to perform the services requested. For example, if you fill out a "Contact Me" Web form, the Company will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in the Service.

The Company may also use Data about EZFacility Customers for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in EZFacility, the Service, and to send you information regarding the Company and its partners, such as information about promotions or events.

EZFacility uses credit card information solely to check the financial qualifications of prospective Customers and to collect payment for the Service.

EZFacility uses Web Site Navigational Information to operate and improve the Company’s Web sites. The Company may also use Web Site Navigational Information in combination with Data about EZFacility Customers to provide personalized information about the Company.

### Web Site Navigational Information

EZFacility uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons, to collect information as you navigate the Company’s Web sites ("Web Site Navigational Information") . This section describes the types of Web Site Navigational Information the Company may collect and how the Company may use this information.

#### Cookies

EZFacility uses cookies to make interactions with the Company’s Web sites easy and meaningful. When you visit one of the Company’s Web sites, EZFacility’s servers send a cookie to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you. They merely recognize your Web browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to EZFacility, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or filling out a Web form (such as a "Contact Me" or a "Free Trial" Web form), you remain anonymous to the Company.

There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer.

If you have chosen to identify yourself to EZFacility, the Company uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the Company to uniquely identify you. Each time you log into the Service, a session cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account is placed your browser. These session cookies allow the Company to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the Service and to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies are required to use the Service.

EZFacility uses persistent cookies that only the Company can read and use to identify browsers that have previously visited the Company’s Web sites. When you purchase the Service or provide the Company with personal information, a unique identifier is assigned you. This unique identifier is associated with a persistent cookie that the Company places on your Web browser. The Company is especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, the Company does not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. If you disable your Web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you will be able to navigate the Company’s Web sites, but you will not be able to successfully use the Service.

EZFacility may use information from session and persistent cookies in combination with Data about EZFacility Customers to provide you with information about the Company and the Service.

#### Web Beacons

EZFacility uses Web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about Customers and Visitors’ usage of the Company’s Web sites and interaction with emails from the Company. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular Web site tied to the Web beacon, and a description of a Web site tied to the Web beacon. For example, EZFacility may place Web beacons in marketing emails that notify the Company when you click on a link in the email that directs you to one of the Company’s Web sites. EZFacility uses Web beacons to operate and improve the Company’s Web sites and email communications. EZFacility may use information from Web beacons in combination with Data about EZFacility Customers to provide you with information about the Company and the Service.

#### IP Addresses

When you visit EZFacility’s Web sites, the Company collects your Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses to track and aggregate non-personally identifiable information. For example, EZFacility uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which Customers and Visitors navigate the Company’s Web sites.

EZFacility also collects IP addresses from Customers whey they log into the Service as part of the Company’s "Identity Confirmation" and "IP Range Restrictions" security features.

#### Third Party Cookies

From time-to-time, EZFacility engages third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from individuals who visit the Company’s Web sites. EZFacility may also use other third-party cookies to track the performance of Company advertisements. The information provided to third parties does not include personal information, but this information may be re-associated with personal information after the Company receives it. This Privacy Statement does not cover the use of third party cookies.

#### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Public Forums, Refer a Friend, and Customer Testimonials

EZFacility may provide bulletin boards, blogs, or chat rooms on the Company’s Web sites. Any personally identifiable information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums, and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. EZFacility is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@ezfacility.com](mailto:support@ezfacility.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Customers and Visitors may elect to use the Company’s referral service to inform friends about the Company’s Web sites. When using the referral service, the Company requests the friend’s name and email address. EZFacility will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Company’s Web sites. EZFacility does not store this information.

EZFacility posts a list of Customers and testimonials on the Company’s Web sites that contain information such as Customer names and titles. EZFacility obtains the consent of each Customer prior to posting any information on such a list or posting testimonials. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@ezfacility.com](mailto:support@ezfacility.com).

### Sharing of Information Collected

EZFacility may share Data about EZFacility Customers with the Company’s agents so that these agents can contact Customers and Visitors who have provided contact information on our behalf. EZFacility may also share Data about EZFacility Customers with the Company’s agents to ensure the quality of information provided. EZFacility does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

EZFacility uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on the Company’s behalf.

EZFacility reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information of the Company’s Customers or Visitors if required by law or if the Company reasonably believes that disclosure is necessary to protect the Company’s rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. If EZFacility is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

### Communications Preferences

EZFacility offers Customers and Visitors who provide contact information a means to choose how the Company uses the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of the Company’s marketing emails. Additionally, you may send a request specifying your communications preferences to [support@ezfacility.com](mailto:support@ezfacility.com). Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with EZFacility or the Service.

### Correcting and Updating Your Information

Customers may update or change their registration information by editing their user or organization record. To update a user profile, please login to [https://secure.ezfacility.com](https://secure.ezfacility.com/) with your EZFacility username and password and click "Administration / User Administration." To update your organization’s information, please login [https://secure.ezfacility.com](https://secure.ezfacility.com/) with your EZFacility username and password and select "Administration / Location/Facility Setup." To update Billing Information or have your registration information deleted, please email support@ezfacility.com or call (516)349-1999. To discontinue your account and to have information you maintained in the Service returned to you, please email [support@EZFacility](mailto:support@ezfacility.com) or call (516) 349-1999. Requests to access, change, or delete your information will be handled within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Customer Data

EZFacility Customers use the Service to host data and information ("Customer Data"). EZFacility will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in the EZFacility Master Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law. Individual records of Customer Data may be viewed or accessed only for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violation of the EZFacility Master Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law. Customers are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of their EZFacility usernames and passwords.

### Security

EZFacility uses robust security measures to protect Customer Data from unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and help ensure the appropriate use of Customer Data. When the Service is accessed using Internet Explorer version 6.0 or later, Firefox version 2.0 or later, or Safari version 3.0 or later, Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology protects Customer Data using both server authentication and data encryption. These technologies help ensure that Customer Data is safe, secure, and only available to the Customer to whom the information belongs and those to whom the Customer has granted access. EZFacility also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and the Company hosts its Web sites in a secure server environment that uses firewalls and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. EZFacility also offers enhanced security features within the Service that permit Customers to configure security settings to the level they deem necessary.

Because the Company uses the Service to maintain Data about EZFacility Customers, this information is secured in the same manner as described above for Customer Data.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

EZFacility reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement. EZFacility will provide notification of the material changes to this Privacy Statement through the Company’s Web sites at least thirty (30) business days prior to the change taking effect.

### Contacting Us

Questions regarding this Privacy Statement or the information practices of the Company’s Web sites should be directed to EZFacility Privacy by emailing [info@ezfacility.com](mailto:info@ezfacility.com) or by mailing EZFacility, 67 Froehlich Farm Blvd., Woodbury, NY, 11797.
